You take a turn, I take a turn
Can you guys not play so intensely?
They want to lose, right?
Yes
Choose someone of the opposite sex to drink a toast with
Xiao Hu is about to cry
I want to lose too
But
The opportunity is on your side
He used this laugh
to bring out the laughter in his heart
He was happy
He made a circle with his hands
and let the other person enter the circle
Look at his laugh
Tomorrow night
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Yes, I do
Xiao Hu
This is for you
Thank you
Would you like to go on a date tomorrow for New Year?
Sure
The joy of true fans
Happy New Year
Quickly get on the Soul APP
Interesting souls, free encounters
This show is exclusively sponsored by
Soul APP, which young people are all using
Global beauty and health products
On Watsons mini program
Thanks to healthy beauty, beautiful health
Jointly sponsored by Watsons
Welcome friends to
Tencent Video's original
Mature love observation reality show
"Half Mature Lovers" Season 4
We meet again
I am Xie Nan
We also want to welcome
Our old friends in the observation room
And new friends
We welcome Teacher Du Sujuan
Xu Yiyang
Chun Ye
Tang Yixin
Lu Hu
Xia Zhiguang
Next, let's quickly go to the Half Mature House
To see their dates
What will happen
Looking forward to it
Do you want to eat dumplings?
Okay.
But I...
You're leaving.
Is it too late to make dumplings now?
To be honest,
I kind of guessed.
A secret invitation last night.
Liang Tian and Hu Yunting went on a date.
Not having dumplings?
I think there's not enough time.
We are leaving at thirty minutes past.
I was just being polite.
You are going to play all day?
Going out since the morning.
You will never understand in your lifetime
I don't understand
That hand must be in the pocket
Old Hu
To be honest
Before this
Who is he actually interested in
I really can't tell
He just can't see it
Otherwise, he wouldn't eat so much beef noodles
Really
Three bowls
He finished all the beef noodles
He just came to Old Hu's pot
I was a bit worried
You wouldn't be eyeing the bread again, would you
Teacher Luo is so cute
Today is all about enjoyment
Yes
Actually, I found out
that now in the small house
many people are being friendly with Liang Tian
Yonghao is actually interested in her
Brother Luo probably has feelings for her too
I told him
I asked how to judge his feelings
how to judge his feelings
how to judge
you talked to me about it
all the girls are
all impossible
you haven't considered it for now
what an eye roll
you didn't mention it to me
you are still unsure in your heart
after I suddenly thought of it yesterday
I realized in a flash
so that's how it is
so it's still like this
you should think about yourself
bro, what are you doing
eating melons, eating others' melons
really
so from that
playing that Cyber Jump
did you already have that idea
they started chatting
these three gathered together
Cyber Jump
Cyber Step Light (game)
Really?
Bro
Kept asking
Just slowly
But you must enjoy it first
You must enjoy it first
Yes
Enjoyment is important
I'm still learning
Su Yonghao's aggressiveness is still a bit strong
But shouldn't we teach him some bad tricks
To ruin him
Stay with me.
Is there any sense of crisis?
I think it's fine.
I'll try to seize every opportunity in the next few days.
Spend time with her.
Make them give up.
Always says some very harsh things in a calm manner.
Yes, he always has a calm expression.
But his words are intense.
He's quite ruthless.
This one is ready
Why is it every morning
I see a man in the kitchen
Happy
Brother
Seeing him so happy
I really envy you
Always this happy every day
Everything is going well for you
Yes, very well
Really
When did you get the flowers
I bought the flowers yesterday afternoon
Yes
Afternoon
It looks like you weren't planning to go out
Yes
Do you want some bacon
I won't eat
I'm done eating
I'll eat
I also want to try the love bacon
Why is this bacon so sweet
Did you add honey
No, I didn't
I added love
Goodbye
Enjoy your date
Now you know
Got it
I see
You're amazing
Really
I'll ask you out next time
Goodbye
Have fun
You too
Wowo also jumped out
Happy little steps
What's there to eat here
There's bread over there
And there's yogurt
I'll have some bread
Then I can make you some eggs
Who made all this breakfast
Who
Who is so nice
What's up
Hot
Could this be
something someone specially prepared for you?
No
It's not prepared for her
This is Luo Junfan's New Year gift for you
Thank you
Leaving
So it's mine
Won't you let her have some?
No need
She doesn't need to eat
She doesn't like it
Doesn't like it
Goodbye
Yes
Yes, I don't like it
Because she didn't take breakfast last time
Missed it, it was a misunderstanding
Mutual misunderstanding
It's another beautiful day
Yes, it is
So we
are going to eat first?
Or what?
Where is the food?
Then why haven't you opened the breakfast yet?
This is a sad story.
Not a happy story.
What exactly
Classmate, have you eaten breakfast?
Wait a moment.
So that's how it is.
Sorry.
Classmate, have you eaten breakfast?
No, I haven't.
I haven't either.
But I brought a sandwich.
But there's only one.
Not for you.
Because they said you don't like it.
So
you seek revenge.
Smells good.
You don't have anything to eat, do you?
That's great.
So annoying.
Smells really good.
I'm really impressed.
But some people don't have anything to eat.
It's a bit of a pity.
How much longer do we have to wait?
When there's breakfast.
Thank you.
So romantic
I quite enjoy watching this kind of
little tricks of young couples
When I saw the bread on the table
I asked whose breakfast this was
I picked it up and looked at it
It must have been made for someone
Then I thought to myself
You definitely wouldn't make breakfast today
Because you were hurt yesterday
No, I wouldn't
I'm the thick-skinned type
I was a bit puzzled yesterday
Everyone was downstairs eating
You know
Then I went downstairs and sat there
It felt like everyone was acting unnatural
I was thinking, why are you all acting unnatural
You guys are the ones who are behind
And you still have the nerve to mock this
Right
The students who are good at studying
The students who are good at reading
Then they said
I'll tell you a sad story
They said this morning when they opened the fridge
We were still thinking
Whether or not
Whether or not to secretly take it and eat it
Whether or not to help WoWo eat it
Then
Really
They are really nice
Why does WoWo seem like a straight guy
The two of them are quite fun
Right
How does your brain work?
No, you didn't say it was in the fridge.
You just told me to remember to eat breakfast.
I understood it as
that even though you don't need me to make breakfast anymore,
you should remember to eat breakfast yourself.
Okay.
Then from now on, I have to write
in the second shelf of the fridge,
remember to take it.
Next time, I'll write the word "Wowo"
as big as possible.
Sis, it can't be any bigger, sis.
Everyone
Everyone is already caring about you.
Right?
Let me show you last night
the fireworks they set off.
Really,
I missed that moment.
When my friends were setting off fireworks together,
I specifically recorded a video of the fireworks.
Although we didn't celebrate the New Year together,
I hope to share
what I saw at that moment
with her.
I don't want her to miss anything
Whose perspective is this, who is holding it?
It's me
I thought you were passing it around
Sis, I'm going to make you so mad, sis
No, I'm too angry
Tonight
We will aim at your room
and set off Gatling fireworks
Thank you
and then light up your room
Look at the things you're saying
They don't even count as cold jokes
Last night
Teacher Liang sang a song
Her original song
Was it last night or this morning
I heard Yonghao singing
Because he is next door to me
Then it must be hard for you to sleep well
It's okay, it's still quiet
Since Yonghao always sings and disturbs your sleep
Then tonight
I'll go back and tell him
to sing louder in the future
I'll buy him a megaphone tonight
and sing after ten o'clock at night
so I can go over and sing too
turn his room into a karaoke room
Wowo doesn't want to
He's become so childish now
turn it into a karaoke room
So this is the kind of person you are
I'm starting to understand you a little bit now
You and my first impression of you
are actually not that similar
I thought you were the kind of guy
who is rather shy
and didn't expect you to be like this
it will definitely be better once you get to know everyone
No
you get worse once you get to know everyone
worse
Yes
During the whole conversation
I suddenly realized that he's different
he has a bit of a childish vibe
Is it this way?
Yes, it's this way.
An ideal life
This is the place I like
This shot looks amazing
It feels like when people come to a place like this
they will feel completely renewed
Because she has a lot of stress at work
So I hope
to let her have a good rest
and relax
Take a photo
You're not taking a selfie
When have I ever taken a selfie? I rarely do
I can't even find any photos
I always take pictures of landscapes
Group photos
Or candid shots
Candid shots mean secretly taking selfies
Right
I just realized
We have a new
King of bad jokes
Did you set this wallpaper yourself
Yes
Now I'm a cute little girl
This is the
Coldest
Coldest joke I've heard today
Coming from your mouth
That you're a cute little girl
Set mine like that when you get home tonight
What
Set it as a cute little girl too
No need
Okay
I like this kind
There are sheep over there
These sheep
So cute
It's a bit hyperactive
You are wearing light colors today, and this
matches well with this sheep, right?
Let's go give it some vegetable leaves.
Sure.
Come on, Wowo, it's time for breakfast.
I really thank you.
You are such a person.
Hurry up.
Everyone is here.
So scary.
Don't bump into me.
Quick, put it down.
I think it's a bit dangerous.
The situation is getting a bit out of control.
Then this little one just
comes to feed the little lamb.
Its teeth are so white.
What's wrong with you?
Don't lift it too high.
Then it might kick you.
How did it stand up?
It's too high for you.
Don't hold it so high.
Just put it a bit lower.
Why does it keep hurting you?
You said his height is just right
Keep kicking him
I'm laughing to death
Are there any injuries from the kick?
No, I'm fine.
Just a bit dirty.
Let's go.
What is this place?
It looks a bit like a wedding venue.
There might be a proposal or something over there today.
Look, it really seems like it, right?
Yes.
When we went over, we found that
I had plastered your photos everywhere.
Yes.
I said this was a bit too fast, right?
Take a look
The love letter has only three lines
Look, they already got their certificate
Yes, they already got their certificate
This is the male lead
They filmed this very well
They must have traveled to many places
Sit for a while.
Let's go.
So interesting.
Crayon Shin-chan.
I think it's after getting the certificate.
And then we still need to
add a proposal.
Yes, because this really
doesn't look like a wedding scene.
I looked at it, it really doesn't.
This is quite good.
It has a sense of ceremony.
This also took a lot of effort.
and thought.
So do you think guys
care about this sense of ceremony?
Or do they think girls want it
so they do it?
You like this sense of ceremony
For example, this kind
I think such things are necessary
I think such a big event
I think the significance of proposing is
The significance of proposing is
In not agreeing
In what
In not agreeing, right
No
Usually, women might be more eager to enter marriage
But generally speaking, men
might
not be as eager as women
But if a man proposes
at least I think at that moment
it proves that the man is very proactive
wanting to
send himself into the grave of love, right?
No, so no
It's just very proactive to cover himself up
proving that I am more eager than you
to solidify this relationship
So listen, you see
I think
you still have a relatively optimistic attitude towards marriage
maintaining a relatively optimistic attitude
not a repulsive or resistant
kind of thought
I have come into contact with many people
both men and women
and they would give me
the message or idea that
they think
that marriage might be the grave of love
After marriage, you have to face daily necessities
face many trivial matters of life
They are very worried that this
will gradually diminish the feeling of love
Actually, regarding these people's thoughts
I think
I don't really agree
Because my parents' relationship is still
quite good
I often describe my parents' relationship
as a relationship that requires constant mending
They often talk about who got divorced
who broke up
I stopped believing in love
But when I see
my parents together
I still feel quite hopeful
Hopeful
Yes, hopeful
Actually, I think you
It's quite rare for guys to be like this
It really seems quite rare
At least from my perspective
What do you think is
the reason for their lack of hope?
I think it's actually
that they might have a pessimistic attitude towards their future
life
They are more sensitive to negative cases
and situations
Because nowadays, many single people stay safe
and things like that
including the worst cases
even involving money and life
are related to those things
but I feel it doesn't affect me at this moment
still
I still have aspirations, right
Yes
Your mindset is very optimistic
Optimistically maintaining a small expectation
We are quite similar.
Our views on marriage are also
aligned.
They are quite similar.
Have we talked this deeply?
We've talked this much.
Actually, sometimes when I think of you,
I feel that
you are a very direct and bold guy.
Just direct.
For example, you dare to post my name
on Moments.
You really always
surprise me.
I feel that right now,
there isn't a guy
with your style.
Does it make you uncomfortable?
That's a good question.
I don't feel uncomfortable.
But you know, I really
always find it hard to believe.
For example, in front of everyone,
you say I'm your crush.
Then maybe in the future, no other girl
might choose to date you.
You didn't leave yourself a way out.
Trying to interact with various girls
or something.
But I don't need that anymore.
Anyway, you are my first choice.
It will never change.
You two have learned this here
Watching this episode, I've learned too much from him
From now on, it's Brother Hou for me
I won't call him Little Hou anymore, really
I am quite decisive when it comes to relationships.
And I am not a proactive person.
But I am a rather brave person.
I am a bit
Actually, I am a bit of a romantic among guys.
Yes, you are a romantic.
I am quite rare among guys.
Yes, I can feel that.
You really are a romantic.
He suddenly appeared
I call him "little love brain"
His so-called love brain
actually makes me feel that he
gives me a feeling
that this relationship is usually quite stable
or has a sweet feeling
Today's date
brought us even closer
I was actually a bit worried before
every time I was alone with her
but today I felt much more relaxed
and much happier
without any burden
I couldn't help but want to get closer
and it brought us even closer
Can this bread be eaten or not?
We didn't eat enough, right?
Why didn't you eat in the morning?
She started to show a bit of concern
in a complaining way
I never eat breakfast
Never
You, who don't eat breakfast
you can actually make breakfast
I am really a bit touched
So I forgive you for making it like that
Is it that bad?
It's just a bit salty
Actually, there's no other problem
Did you rest well?
Pretty good.
Liang Tian's speaking condition
Did you rest well?
It was okay.
You two really found partners.
When you received that task yesterday,
what did you think?
Just your first reaction.
The first reaction was
to look up and see where the person was.
Because I went to get my phone
I saw the message as soon as it arrived
Then I saw the guys washing the dishes
I wanted to say
I have a little time
I forgot who came over to tell you
Take a break
Mr. Liang, if you're okay, just go to sleep
You're still not feeling well
Okay
So I just looked like
I had an opportunity
I wanted to say
It's already
I heard you were going to rest
Then I feel like I should leave first
Maybe it will work out
Yunting these past two days
His initiative
I could clearly sense it
The person you're interested in
And he also actively showed his goodwill towards you
For me
That's definitely a good thing
This feeling is also very good
It's like we're hiding from the world
We did some things together
The feeling of our little secret
We're almost there
This road is so beautiful
Forest Park
Taking a picture like this
It really looks great
We went to the park today
Extremely, extremely beautiful
You can sunbathe
You can rent a kayak
The atmosphere is quite relaxed
I hope we can fully enjoy this moment
This one is good too
It's a bit beautiful
There's sunshine
Happy
Life jacket pickup point
Come on
Thank you
Is this how you wear it?
Yes
Okay
Do you know how to swim?
I do know how to swim.
But since you're asking,
I think I can.
But it's best not to need to use
this survival skill.
I hope we won't need it either.
Let's go.
Thank you
You are good at this
I am off balance
Be careful
Thank you
Slow down
Okay
This is interesting.
This is the redwood.
That red tree.
So beautiful.
I feel like we can
paddle to an open area.
Let's not move anymore.
Just lie down.
Yes, just lie down.
This place is so comfortable.
Let's float for a while.
Not moving.
The weather is just right
The sunlight is just right
I just want to stop in the middle of that lake
I don't want to move
Such a comfortable and pleasant day
So comfortable
I'll take a few pictures for you.
Three, two, one.
Three pictures, right?
Yes.
Looks good.
Thank you.
Starting to be naughty
The waves are big
Starting to be mischievous
Danger
Dangerous move
The waves are big
The waves are huge
Captain
Keep acting along
If the phone falls into this river
What should we do
Then we carve one on this boat
Just carve a horizontal line
Then when we reach the shore
Just follow this horizontal line
Reach out and find it
We need to try to go through the small door
Go through the small door?
Are we challenging the limits?
Let's challenge it
Wait a moment
Let's not hit the tree first
First, aim not to hit the tree
This is good
Help
Okay, I'm lying down.
Okay.
Airplane.
Is this direction towards Pudong?
Pudong.
Flying from Hongqiao to Pudong, right?
Today's date with Liang Tian
was actually very happy.
Very healing.
A bit like retirement life.
It matches well.
On a trail under the redwoods.
Blowing bubbles.
Actually, a bit like a child.
Just a very simple date.
Very comfortable.
I felt that she quietly
was paying attention to me.
and cooperating with me.
So I felt quite happy.
Catch it
Can you blow
a really, really big bubble
and cover me with it
It should
It should be a bit difficult
You fly away by yourself
Today is January 1st.
New Year's wishes.
I hope my family stays healthy.
Safe.
And happy.
I hope this year goes smoothly.
Every year at the beginning,
I make a wish list for myself.
This year's list.
One of the wishes is,
I want to go to Yunnan to visit Xia Xia.
This wish should be easy to achieve.
I think she will be very excited.
These episodes are quite exciting.
Okay.
Get ready to hang the lock, friends.
Hang the lock for our victory.
Just the two of us, right?
Come.
Come on.
Friends who have won.
Applause here.
No wonder they are "Love Researchers" and "Flow of Heart".
Come on, friends
About those two dates just now
How do you feel
Huzi took a bunch of notes again
Yes, true fans
I really think
A good relationship can withstand the test of time
The first day she came back
had a strong sense of "death"
And I saw
they were sharing with each other
everything they missed yesterday
everything
I want to share everything with you
I don't want to miss out
Yes, there were fireworks
and then singing
This is so important
This is very important, it's really great
When you usually have to be apart from Xuxu
when you are separated
what do you do
you will share with her
Do you encounter this at work
This must be shared
I found that missing someone
sometimes it's not about the person
but the moments spent with them
every single moment
Sharing can help us
resolve many things in life
whether it's missing someone
sometimes even
it can resolve conflicts
and it makes the other person feel
that they are always being thought of
Yes
I think it's a
very deep and effective communication
But I have a friend
who is an example of the opposite.
They are also in a long-distance relationship.
Her husband is quite strict.
She has to, every hour,
send her husband
what she is eating,
who she is with,
and take pictures of who she is with.
I think this kind of sharing
is not something I agree with in a relationship.
Because you are sharing information,
but what we actually want to share
are feelings.
Yes.
Not a report of information.
I particularly care about
the nature of sharing.
I especially give a good response
to those who share with me.
Yes.
Of course.
Because I think the desire to share
is a very fragile feeling.
It is easily hurt.
It is easily discouraged.
Because the desire to share
if I say it once,
If he doesn't respond
I feel like he doesn't really care
or doesn't really like it
Then he shares it with me
I feel like I have a
unique feeling in the world
So I think this thing
has a unique quality
Because actually I am a
person with a strong desire to share
Yes, just like you said earlier
the desire to share is easily broken
Yes
At the beginning, because of
this desire to share
I doubted whether
Tao and I were suitable for each other
because he really doesn't like
using the phone for a relationship
For example, when I am on a business trip
we might not contact each other
for the whole day
And because of this
I have mentioned it many times
At the beginning
I would say it very tactfully
Later, I would say it directly
Won't you reply?
Can't you see?
Yes
But this process of adjustment
is very important
After adjusting, now
we are mutually equal
If we want to respond to each other, we do
If we don't want to respond
we don't respond
Now you don't send it, he does.
That's how it is now.
Now it's like asking me what I'm doing.
I think you're particularly brave because
you expressed your needs.
Yes.
I will emphasize the importance of the desire to share.
Teach him a lesson, right?
Forward the post to him.
I said, take a look yourself.
Learn a bit
Then after watching, he will accept
Then go and change
I think this process is very important
Guiding type lover
Yes
It's about mutual adjustment
Sharing this behavior is very important
In intimate relationships
The key to sharing is enjoyment
At this time, we need to pay attention
To the content of sharing
So the first aspect of the desire to share
Is that we might
Not be overly self-centered
That the other person doesn't need
Or is unrelated to the other person
But I keep outputting to him
But his sharing
Could turn into nagging
Sharing and nagging are just a step apart
Sharing is ultimately to build a
Shared space
Not just opinions and views
Including mutual friends
Shared life experiences
So regarding the content to share
We need to make some choices
And the final goal must be clear
I want to build a
common ground with you
Just now, Hou mentioned something
He said that among men,
he is a rare "love brain."
I think the term "love brain"
should be used cautiously.
Yes.
I think "love brain" is
when the need for love exceeds love itself.
He excessively relies on the other person.
He has very low self-esteem.
A good relationship is actually
a massage for self-esteem.
When you are with him,
you feel like you become
a better person.
But a "love brain" person
doesn't have high expectations
for the other person.
In fact, their expectations are very low.
I think this is a form of selfishness.
It seems like
I am endlessly giving,
but actually,
he is trying to fulfill
his own needs,
his own desires,
and engages in extreme behaviors.
Ultimately, it is an expression of inferiority,
a selfish act.
It is not love.
Love is actually about fulfilling responsibility and tolerance.
Someone like Brother Hou knows how to date
knows how to love and express love
and knows how to receive love
is actually quite good
I think
if a romantic mindset looks like this
I think a romantic mindset is a plus
But what I understand about being love-struck is
In my mind
I have a part dedicated to being love-struck
But that doesn't mean I don't have other things
So I think a moderate amount of being love-struck
is actually
Yes, it's quite good
Right, it's quite good
More solid
I agree with what you just said
Don't randomly label people
And I also want to say
that everyone shouldn't always judge
others as being love-struck
Yes
Among people in love
their intense dedication
is a very normal thing
So don't be prejudiced or label them
Yes, don't do that
It will stifle the occurrence of true love
Yes
We've talked so much about being love-struck
I'll boldly say
Let's just ship these two right here
Does that count as their true love-struck?
That's perfect.
So, should we give it a name?
As long as you're with the right person
every day is Valentine's Day
so they are "Valentine's Day partners"
and one has the surname Ren
and the other has the name Jie
this is good
Valentine's Day works
Yes, we'll start with a small idea
everyone can come up with names
the comments are definitely the most creative
yes
we'll continue watching
what happens in the next date
okay
Went out by themselves
Why do I want to laugh as soon as Teacher Luo appears?
We are leaving
Sis
Your outfit today is very Korean
Me? Really?
Beautiful
What language?
Korean
Beautiful
I can't learn it
Brother
I love you
So direct?
Has it already started?
I'll make it happen for you
Leaving
Goodbye
Have fun
She is always so full of energy.
We look like monkeys
like gorillas
It's so funny
This scene is so desolate.
Watching them walk away.
Observing.
Is a bowl of yogurt enough for you?
Yes, it's enough.
There's someone watching.
There are too many sad people.
One is at the front door.
One is at the second-floor window.
Really.
Some families are happy, some are sad.
It really is.
Let's go.
He wants to give the other person space.
Yes.
It's over.
I have a feeling
It's not like I originally expected
Those few dates I had with Kaka before
In my opinion, they were
mutually affectionate
with some intimate interactions
But
relax
For someone with her personality
it doesn't necessarily mean anything
She might just be a good friend
She interacts like this with everyone
It might have given me some misconceptions
To be honest
So I chose
to see the answer for myself
I don't want to get involved in this
competitive relationship in emotions
And if one side needs
to gain through such competition
I think from the beginning
it's not the right person
Finally, we are splitting up and moving.
So desolate, our Brother Zhang.
Anti-internal friction
Anti-internal friction psychology
Brother Chen just realized
that Kaka seems to like Yonghao
Yes, he realized he made a mistake
Arrived
Great
Hello
We want to make instruments or something like that
The hardest
Over here
Handmade
So cute
Help
This is too cute
Thumb piano
You will like this handmade item
I really like doing crafts
I think handmade items have warmth
I never thought there would be aprons here
Can't escape the apron
Award ceremony
Award
This is
But love to watch
Even though it's a routine
But
Love to watch
Willing to be caught by it
Never out of style
I haven't used these tools in a long time
These are perfect for you
Easy
Not difficult (for me)
Open
So, these circles are
to increase the thickness, right?
Punch through it
because it might break if you go all at once
Those damn memories are haunting me again
The teacher has some expertise
in their own hands
Yes
I had forgotten before
but now they are back
Speed up
Come on
still following your rhythm
Almost there
Is it Totoro?
So cute
It's okay
Of course
I just feel this scene is very beautiful
This matter is also very beautiful
This feeling is also very beautiful
It makes me feel
He might have some affection for me
This atmosphere is perfect
Perfect
Is it okay?
First, evenly apply this oil over the entire surface
To prevent the wood from cracking and deforming
Okay, I'll do it
It's up to you, teacher
But does your guitar have a special story?
That was when I wanted to travel around the world
I bought a travel guitar
Travel around the world
I also want to travel around the world
Which cities have you visited so far?
Which countries?
I have been to India and Myanmar
And then Singapore
At that time, I was traveling on a budget
I carried my guitar by the roadside
And earned some food
Really?
That's very brave
Yes
In the past, because of this
I argued with my ex several times
Because not everyone wants to have
Such an exciting
Life like this
Now I focus all my energy on the shop
You know, Shanghai is indeed
one of the cities with the highest coffee density
in the world.
And around here, there are actually many people
who open coffee shops in Hengfu.
So, do you want to open one?
There are many coffee shops here.
Some of them are quite famous.
I can take you next time.
Hengfu.
I know a few famous ones.
Although I don't drink coffee,
my friends all do.
I can introduce you to them.
I've been looking for different coffee shops in Shanghai.
Actually, I am testing.
There are some things I want to understand.
There are some things I can test.
Ask about.
Why do you have a feeling that
you are always looking for a place?
Yes, it seems like you don't
just like me,
I really want to stay in Shanghai.
I don't want to go to other cities.
And now you live in Macau, China.
It's not Hong Kong, China, right?
Yes.
I don't think Macau, China is my final destination.
I don't plan to stay in Macau, China in the future.
Is this like Xia Xia's nomadic life?
Is it the same?
Not really.
Maybe.
Actually, my thoughts are similar to hers.
But she is already doing it.
I don't have the ability to work remotely.
That kind of ability.
So I am still working on it slowly.
Your life seems to be on a completely different path from mine.
Completely different.
Very far apart.
Yes.
Alright, it's good to talk about it.
I also had some dreams
but in the end
yes
there might be some issues in implementing them
but I am someone who loves to fantasize
and loves to experience life
because indeed
you can't just dream
there are also practical reasons that
support you to make other choices
or limit you
yes, this is quite good
so your fondness for me only comes from
me giving you tea at that time
so at that time I didn't think too much
because I felt that my life path
was very different from yours
I was worried that
we wouldn't be able to have deep conversations
this was also one of my concerns at that time
I want to find some tea leaves.
But I can't find any.
I'll bring some for you when I go to the city.
Okay.
This is for making coffee for you.
And this is "human courier."
Indeed, I was moved before.
She is really straightforward.
A very sincere person.
I feel she is really like a friend.
More than a romantic partner.
I felt it.
She wants to express more.
A sense of interaction between us.
But I feel it's a bit of a burden.
So you see, Yonghao is also a straightforward person.
Yes.
I think actually there is something.
Actually, it's good for both people to express themselves.
Because I feel that.
Our backgrounds are too different.
I feel we shouldn't think too much about it.
Emotions don't dominate your mind.
Do they?
Yes.
I.
I am someone who suppresses my emotions.
So I am rarely moved by emotions.
So I can understand the tea leaves situation
as just a gesture of appreciation?
Yes
I think it's about being noticed
for one's own needs
It's not just a simple gift
It's more like being cared for
Is this okay?
Yes
This is already fine
Okay
Wipe your hands
My overall feeling about today's date
is generally
the overall atmosphere is good
I don't plan to stop
because I think sometimes
some affections can be pursued without hesitation
I have a favorite Cantonese song
It's called "Never"
Never opened soda
It's like some excitement
that doesn't come out
It just doesn't come out
It just stays there forever
But when you want to open this can of soda
you'll think
once it's opened
you can't put it down
Especially good
Actually, I roughly know in my heart
his first choice is Teacher Liang
but for me
I have made up my mind
to be brave for once
to accomplish something like this
I need to make an effort
a soda that will never be opened
let me hold it in my arms and kiss it
You're back.
Little Fruit
On the hour
Finished reading (the book)
Finished reading
You didn't say anything
I didn't disturb you, did I?
No
I think your song is pretty good.
When you read a book,
No,
I don't mind noise when I read.
I find you particularly
considerate of others.
Eat.
Do I really deserve such high praise?
I think so myself.
Brother, why are you staying here today?
I didn't want to go out with anyone yesterday.
You didn't go to the appointment.
I didn't.
So I basically gave up this opportunity.
I want to take a break.
I want to give myself some breathing time.
And give others some breathing time too.
Anyway, I'm following my heart.
They are about to start.
Brother Luo is really a bit dazed.
I feel today
that sometimes
life slows down a bit
it can make your
feelings change.
Yes.
So boring.
You are so mean.
Speak properly.
Let's not hurt each other.
They seem quite serious.
Yeah, don't do that.
Think before you speak, okay?
Be careful when you speak.
These two look like a couple.
Speak properly later.
Yes.
They already have that little feeling.
Yes, they have that feeling.
Like a young married couple.
Yes.
Remind him.
So warm.
Yes, think before you act.
Go over and see what they are talking about.
Aren't you supposed to think before you act?
You have to do it.
If it really doesn't work, then it doesn't work.
The main thing is to say hello.
Yes, just go over and say hello.
Someone has returned.
What are you two talking about so seriously?
You came back so quickly.
Yes.
I'm very tired today.
Then we came back.
Think about it again.
Mr. Luo reacts quickly to other people's problems.
Yes.
He really reacts quickly to other people's problems.
He reacts especially quickly.
Think about it again.
What to say.
Think before you act.
What are you saying?
I'll go up first.
Where did you two cut this thing?
I'll cut it for you.
That's great.
Here you go.
I peeled it for you
Really, being outside made me so thirsty and hungry
Comrade Wowo
I have a question to ask
Did you see the note on the sandwich that day
Did you see it
This matter
I have explained it eight hundred times already
Did you see it?
In my heart, I think you should be
Didn't see it
I have seen it eight hundred times
No, this matter
It's okay, the misunderstanding is resolved
It's not like that anymore
You see, kind people are comforting me
Yesterday
I spent the day being comforted by them
Did you see it?
I saw it
I am a meticulous
and detail-oriented person
He told me to remember to eat breakfast
So I immediately thought
it meant to buy breakfast yourself in the morning
Yes
That's how I understood it at the time
I swear that's what I thought
Your
This explanation makes sense
This explanation is very reasonable
Really
Understood
This explanation is very smooth
This is indeed very smooth
He is still helping others over there
Help yourself, what are you doing here?
This Luo Junfan
has already forgotten why he came here
He worries about everyone except himself
This is very smooth
This is indeed very smooth
I am really rushed in the morning
You know, 10 seconds in the morning for me
is very rushed
I know
Drink your hot water first
What is he doing here?
He thought, what else can I do for you?
I really give up, really.
Brother Zhang
What's wrong
He acts like a child
Those two are so disgusting
So disgusting
You need to learn to be immune to these things
It's so cold.
What are they doing?
Finally back.
Someone from their group is back.
What are they doing?
They're chatting.
Someone else is back.
Everyone is early today.
I'll go open the door for them.
They might not know the code.
Do you know the code?
I thought...
I was afraid you couldn't get in.
Where did you two go?
You two...
We went to play pickleball.
Pickleball.
Yan Xing.
When we're together, I feel...
No social pressure.
Beautiful.
It didn't hit my paddle.
It's all your fault.
It's like
we've known each other for a long time
like friends
a very relaxed feeling
friends
and like friends who have known each other for a long time
yes
Hello everyone
Scared to death
Chen, you scared to death
Kaka
Put those things here first
Okay
What are you going to do?
We are preparing to cook a Western meal.
Make a soup.
One.
Grill a chicken steak.
We prepared portions for two people.
Is this much okay?
It's enough.
I once had a dream in my heart.
Is there anything I can help with?
It's nothing.
How about I do it this way
I won't open the lower leg bone
Alright
Only opened the upper leg bone
Okay
Then I'll make a cut here
Alright
This one needs to be opened too, right
Does this side need to be opened
I can observe some details
Her condition today
is still quite obvious
It should be pointing to Yonghao
Alright, what should I do next, teacher
Watch my performance
Grab a small stool and sit next to you
Okay
Hormones are everywhere
Now
If a female guest could come to me
Even if she is in the Arctic
I would go to accompany her
I think it will happen soon
In half an hour, it should happen
She's here
She really came
There's more
She's here
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
You scared me
I also thought
The female guest arrived
There really is
As soon as we mentioned her arrival, she arrived
Yes
Sit down, the female guest is here
Xia Xia went out by herself
She didn't stay in the cabin like the two boys
My piano
This is the person you missed
Xia Xia is back
You spent quite a long time on these nails
Just take them off
Take them off
Then I went on a date by myself
I went to watch a movie
Really
Any good movies recently?
I went to see "Little Me"
How was the performance?
A bit melancholic, to be honest
Definitely
It must be melancholic
But it should be noted that the acting was quite good.
Xia Xia simply doesn't want to deal with him.
The desire to share stopped abruptly here.
Yes.
She can't share anymore.
Melancholy, perhaps.
It's easy to feel melancholy lately, isn't it?
No.
I'm fine.
It's okay, Teacher Luo.
Everything will get better.
You really said it in a way that makes people...
I curse you to stay at home from now on.
Impossible.
I have to go to work every day.
At least I have a job to go to.
I can't laugh.
In this small room, there are only single-choice questions.
At the same time, when you accept someone,
you will inevitably miss someone else.
So, in that situation,
making a decision
might be immature.
It might also ruin
your future with this person.
I feel guilty about Xia Xia.
Still calmly analyzing here and there.
He has some confidence.
Today is a new year.
A new day.
I don't want to
feel trapped
or have a gloomy mood.
So I chose to go out alone.
I went on a date with myself.
I wanted to give myself a New Year's gift.
This is the sweetest couple
So comfortable
That little lake is really beautiful
This lake
The small water surface
Its water is similar to ours today
It still has that ambiance
Still living by the water
Really nice
They are back
Turns out we are the last
We are the last
I thought we would be first
We were so confident
Why did it take us so long
Are they coming back to eat
Only the two of us ate outside
Because you said we must eat
So
I was being reckless
Time to eat, friends
Hello everyone
Hello
Dinner is ready
We have already eaten
Your outfits today are so well-matched.
Someone even helped highlight the key points, look.
Stab the knife into the heart.
What language assassin?
You two are wearing matching couple outfits.
Where are you going?
Where are you going to have fun?
We are going to the park.
After we finish at the park.
We really went to the park.
Walking around the park is super fun.
Let's go boating.
This is what you like.
Hurry up.
Hurry up and put things away.
Alright, let's go put things away.
Actually, from the very beginning.
I have a relatively clear understanding of Liang Tian's thoughts
I have a relatively clear understanding
She wants to interact more with different
boys she likes
This is expected to happen
So my fondness for her won't decrease
Instead, I give her space
What is it
Just broke
Heartbroken, right
Heartbroken
With a snap
Let's eat
Come on
Let me see what you are eating
Tell us what you ate first
Went to eat Western food
In a farm
But once inside, the table
was a rectangular table
I sat here, he sat there
Then we had a meal
Western food
What is Su Nan doing?
Where did you go?
Anyway, I just went to a park
Had a meal
Then where did you go?
We went to make a musical instrument.
Make what?
The one in front of you, the thumb piano.
Make a musical instrument.
Make this.
It's very fun.
How do you play this?
Thumb piano.
Thank you
Would you like to add some black pepper?
This is your unique (dinner)
Aren't you two full from eating such a big piece?
What is it?
None for you
It's okay, Teacher Luo
If you want to eat, I can share some with you
Yonghao went out with Kaka during the day
It feels like he is deliberately
giving me some space
At that moment, I felt
to make the situation better
it would be better if I stepped back a bit
I think it would be better if it were more charred
Yes, it can be grilled more
But now it's quite tender
If it were more charred, it would be more fragrant
Give her some space
It doesn't mean I'm backing down
On the contrary
I should really find a good opportunity
to communicate with her
What did you all do?
Ask again.
What did you do today?
We went for a walk in the park.
Enjoying retirement life.
Then we went boating.
Sister, you sit at the bow.
Brother walks on the shore.
This joke is really a bit far-fetched.
No one picks up these jokes when you're not around.
I can't do it.
Come on, do you know how to play?
I don't know how to play.
You grab these two.
Teacher Luo.
You are indeed the same age as me.
The same age.
Played this when we were kids.
How do you play this?
Do you know how to play this?
How do you do this?
How do you play this?
This won't work.
This is a dead end.
I don't know either.
No
But after you finish hooking it like this
Immediately
Hook this
But this is tied again
Yes, that's right
What's wrong with this
Mr. Su is going to take action
Going alone to the meeting
Does it have a formula
Yes
It has a formula
Pulling up from below, right
Yes
Yes, you can pull up or down
So innocent
It's all muscle memory
Muscle memory
How does everyone know
Yes
Indeed, we are from different generations
Different generations
I really don't know
Indeed, we are from different generations
I really can't
How do you play this?
Can someone teach me?
How is this played?
Very accurate
It's okay
Do you want to play?
Okay
Great strength creates miracles
Ten
Can
Very sudden
Come on, friends
First, we saw this scene
The date of the craft group
It's Su Yonghao and Kaka
It feels like Kaka still wants
to try a bit harder
Yes
If she is willing for love
to step out of her boundaries
I think it's not impossible
It depends on how much she wants to fight for this relationship
how much she is willing to strive for
Because I think in this situation
they might still need one more
clear communication
Maybe next time
Yonghao might be more clear
in telling her
that it might not be because
of our backgrounds
but rather that he doesn't have feelings for her
He's still too tactful, isn't he?
Because everyone can see Liang Tian
Yes, Liang Tian and Xiao Hu
already seem very locked in
So it might not be impossible
to make some changes
to express something
Yes, my feeling is that it might be
Kaka needs to respect more
the extent of her commitment to this relationship
where my acceptance level is
to what extent
Yes
I think it's enough
She might need to think it through herself
Yes
And in my feelings
most boys and girls
girls might be moved and pursued
to be influenced
but boys might
rarely be pursued
and accept because of being moved
Yes
I think boys are rare
Tiger, would you?
For example, if you don't like a girl
I feel the same way as you
Yes
But if Kaka wants
if she hasn't figured it out
she wants to be more certain
before falling in love
having a chance to practice love
is a good thing
then I wish you courage
I think among them
there is one person who is quite carefree
it's Xia Xia
we see that
although all three are alone
the two guys chose
to stay at home
but she dressed up beautifully
and went out
saying I'm going to have a date with myself
yes
because Xia Xia cried so much before
I was actually a bit worried
but I didn't expect her to be so carefree
yes, what she removed wasn't just her nail polish
she removed the burden in her heart
Huzi really understands
yes
it has to be you
golden words
When I watch dating shows
I am particularly afraid of one thing, which is pairing up
For example, ten men and women
Five men and five women
They must pair up one by one
Pairing up correctly is called balancing
If we balance it
It will convey a very wrong message
Yes
That people must pair up
Right
If I can't pair up
I am broken
I am incomplete
Or in this game rule
I am the loser
Yes, this message is wrong
Actually, in life
We have two states
That can be freely switched
That is called being strong and independent
I can have a partner by my side
And I am with my partner
I am in one state
But I can also be without a partner
I am also independent on my own
This is very powerful
I think Xia Xia
should give us a
more accurate demonstration
I think a big problem right now
including myself
is that we are facing issues
where two people cannot
form a complete circle
and one person alone cannot
This needs to be built
You need to build yourself first
Everyone is independent
But at the same time
We can complement each other
The best state is
Similar personalities, complementary abilities
Yes
It's a relatively good state
I think now maybe
People don't pursue
You are a semicircle, I am a semicircle
To finally form a complete circle
We might all be different shapes
You are an oval, I am a triangle
Yes
But as long as we are together
We have an intersection
Yes
That intersection is enough for the two of us
To form a relationship
A relatively dynamic balance
We agree on this
What shape we each are
Whether we can form a circle
May not be that important
Come on, let's keep watching.
Next, they will have some
heartfelt conversations.
Let's watch together.
Brother Chen
Xiao Su
Showing off your skills again, huh?
No
But I can show you a little trick
Don't stop
I'll take a picture for you
Alright
I sent you a moment on the Soul APP
So that you, Teacher Su
in this highlight moment of the semi-mature house
will have it
Okay
also let me meet more drinking buddies
Alright
Thank you, Brother Chen
Put this here
See who wants to play
Take it yourself
The twelve rules of life
Why does Xiao Hu want
What is he doing
Before this,
I didn't clearly
express my feelings.
So today, I have been
looking for a moment
to properly express to Liang Tian
what's on my mind.
And I hope that after she knows,
she can make a better decision.
She should have felt it.
He has been wandering around nearby, right?
So difficult
He has a lot of little schemes in his mind.
Do you have any questions?
The Book of Answers can tell you.
Are you sure there is anyone?
I originally wanted to say
My question is
Should I tell you now
or should we talk later
Then it directly said
This "Book of Answers" is really (quite magical)
Are you free
Yes, I am free
Then let's go to the study
The study should be empty
Okay
Sneaky
His thing is that he acts like a little boy
They have always been like this
He has that little boy vibe
Full of sneaky feelings "Secret Partner"
"Secret Partner"
Can't hide the secret
Please sit, teacher
Sit
Find a comfortable space
Then I'll sit on this small stool
You sit here
Okay
One thing is,
My views on love are greatly influenced by my parents.
I'm not sure if you noticed,
but my parents are actually divorced.
I can tell.
They argue,
divorce and arguments,
for a long time.
Eventually,
it was for my brother and me,
so we could have a sense of home.
That's why they stayed together.
Watching their relationship,
shaped many of
my current views on love.
I have been in three relationships
but each one around
the three-month mark
I found some difficult problems to solve
In the past, I would immediately think
should I continue or not
so they were all very short
and upon reflection, I feel that
in the past, I was quite one-sided
one-sided in doing this
one-sided in doing what
deciding whether to continue or not
it was always one-sided
yes
and I didn't communicate much
I should say, we didn't find solutions together
yes
I think this time I am changing
I hope to change
because in the past, when I met them
it was quite fast
I felt it was smooth
and after one or two dates
I felt like rushing into it
but now the change I am making
is to slow everything down
first
slowly get to know each other and then discuss things later
okay
what I want to express is
since entering the small house, in our interactions
I always feel
I always pay more attention to you
yes
So that day you ate my breakfast
Actually, happiness came too early
Yes, it felt too fast
It's like
So you feel it's a bit unreal
Instead, it should be slower
Even slower
Right?
Yes
Under this premise
I feel pressured because
I think everyone in the cabin is excellent
And you definitely
In the cabin
There will be many people who like you
I'm not saying
What will happen if you choose me
But if I try too hard to perform
But I don't have that foundation
That's roughly what I want to express
You don't have to
Give me an answer right now
You can think about it slowly
But I hope
After sharing with you
Your time in the cabin
Is to ensure you can experience what you want
Finished talking
Feeling a lot of pressure tonight
Understandable
Happy to hear him say that
He
Willing to express his thoughts more proactively
It shows he has thought it through
This initiative is still remembered
I think you are quite sincere
There are no reservations
Objectively described your
Thoughts and situation
I came to the cabin because
Because it's been over two years since my last relationship
Over two years
Two years
I didn't think much when I came here
My 2025 wish list
Only has one item
Just want to have a good relationship
Actually, I didn't think much
I don't have any long-term goals
coming here
Don't think that just because I'm already thirty-five
I'm not in a hurry at all
So at this age
I won't say that I must
do what people at this age are supposed to do
My family respects me a lot
I even said
Mom, I won't get married in my lifetime
You won't blame me, right?
She said okay
I feel that at this age
there are some things
that I have figured out quite clearly
In the small room
I have a guy that I admire
That day during breakfast
I really am the type
When I saw it was you, I said
I said, I am so lucky
And actually, I
I realized
I might
not be able to ignore you when
we went to Cyber Dance
after that
After
I became interested in you
I think it's normal
Because you are great
But I was thinking
This is rational thinking
I am eight years older than you
But I think being attracted to a soul
is about attraction or something
I think it has nothing to do with age
Regarding my emotions and rationality,
I won't mix them up.
I can roughly guess the underlying
concerns you have.
As I said,
whether I went to meet someone else that day
or did something else,
one reason was to give myself a chance,
and another was that I didn't want to give you
too much pressure.
I think everyone is free.
I feel happy talking like this.
I am very happy.
Thank you.
That's great.
But when we go out,
in what kind of
more natural way
should we talk? We are talking about
talking. We are talking.
No need to think about it.
Everyone can see it.
Who cares, teacher.
Why do you care?
Why think so much?
Didn't we just happen to meet
right at the door?
Wasn't that just a coincidence?
What's going on with you guys?
What are you doing?
It really hurts.
This really hurts.
It's hard to see Su Yonghao in this state.
I am a bit confused
I have tried hard to feel
the feeling towards Kaka
Keep going
I have felt her
hoping to express more
a feeling that we can interact
It's a bit like
there is someone in front of me now
a girl I have feelings for
and
someone who has feelings for me
Then I think
in front of this
who should I choose
You should have an answer yourself.
He came to find Brother Spider.
Let's watch a different movie.
Okay.
Watch my favorite
Okay
Watch "Ponyo on the Cliff"
What do you think about us going out today?
You tell me.
What do you want to say?
How do you feel about us going out today?
You need to ask your own heart.
Why ask me that?
I was just sitting at that boarding gate.
Thinking for half an hour.
When I agreed to go out with you yesterday,
I indeed remembered
the emotion of that moment.
This is what I'm struggling with
So I asked you today
I said
Is it because of the tea leaves?
Because I don't want to say
It's just because of a feeling of being moved
For me
Being moved and liking someone are not the same thing
Yes
But at that time, I would doubt
If that was also a feeling of being touched
Instead, because of this
I couldn't focus on being with you
And have a proper date
I think for you
That is the most irresponsible thing
Because at that time, indeed
You overthink, teacher
I was very happy just now
I really enjoy making that instrument
So you don't need to think too much about it
This is really my business
You don't need to think so much about it
I think I've made myself clear
Even if right now you are
Anyway, I lit the firecracker.
Is this firecracker loud or silent?
I can't try anymore.
I think
you've already made your choice.
You know what you want to do.
But you might be afraid
of causing me a negative reaction.
Or something like that.
I'm fine.
For me,
if we really want to develop,
I feel more attracted to Liang Tian.
Actually, I made it very clear.
I just don't want you
to wait for me unnecessarily.
You actually understand your own feelings, right?
Yes.
That's good too.
I think that
clarifying your own feelings
is a very important thing.
Thank you
It's okay
Kaka is amazing
Both of them are great
After I expressed myself more bravely,
I feel like I have already achieved it.
The things I wanted to do.
So it's enough for me.
Anyway, I'm right here.
You asked if I still like him
I definitely still like him
He firmly chose Liang Tian
I feel a sense of disappointment
His reaction
I also feel I need to think about it
Don't have too many expectations
It's just that between us
We might need some boundaries for now
You need some space, right?
After talking with Kaka
I became even more certain of my feelings
More firmly believe
she can be a very good friend
Indeed, I now want to
interact more with Liang Tian
He can do it too
That's right
His expression has always been good
He explains things clearly without beating around the bush
Going to the park, we definitely need to do something like that
Like flying kites in a drama
No
Not at all
No time
It's okay, what do you want to do?
We sisters are just chatting
Sisters chatting
Don't be nervous
No
Just wanted to see if there's anything to tidy up
Everything is cleaned up
You ran over and said
I want to see if there's anything to tidy up
Then I'll see if there's anything to tidy up
Here to check again
Yes
He just wants to tidy up his mood
You understand him
Yeah
Do you need
any help, teacher?
any help?
Need
Pick up a clean bowl
and then wash it.
You need to dirty the bowl.
When people are embarrassed, they tend to move a lot.
I'm not washing my bowl.
I'm washing my heart.
Can't stay idle, really.
Better give you guys some space.
There's really nothing you can do.
Plenty.
I find it unpleasant to watch.
You do your thing, it's fine.
We're all watching you do it.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Go ahead.
Xia Xia.
Don't really understand.
But I seem to understand a bit.
What about you?
Go ahead.
You went to the media room yesterday
to tell me something
Yes, I just wanted to ask
just
So, I need to give you some space
Right?
Because I'm actually very sensitive
I know
but
I
Just now it was Xia Xia
Didn't Xia Xia leave?
Why is she back again?
She really went to the bathroom
I understand what you mean
I understand how you feel
Don't have too much of that kind of pressure
or any concerns
There aren't any
But I find it very difficult
I used to be
someone who put myself last
I put my family
then friends, career
and then myself
and then what
Yes, that's how I was
Actually, I've always wanted to go with you
to understand more
because I feel with you
I can really talk about what's in my heart
I know
it's just
Hello
What are you doing
Nothing
We were just talking about some
casual things
Beautiful
Let him finish speaking.
What are you doing?
No.
We are just talking about some
casual topics.
Can I join?
Sure.
I'm very curious about you.
Here I am.
Joining in.
Do you feel a lot of pressure?
Actually, I don't feel any pressure.
I'm an outgoing person.
So, are you a male artist
or a female artist
or a versatile artist?
A versatile artist.
This topic
can't be discussed.
Can't talk about it.
Yonghao has left.
Tian Tian didn't respond either
Towards Tian Tian, there's a bit of
avoidance
a slight feeling of avoidance
"Falling Slowly"
Here you go
These two singing this song together
is so funny.
Let me see what's going on.
What's up, bro?
What are you doing?
What's going on tonight
So strange
I can't sing the rest.
I forgot too.
This song really matches his mood.
It seems slow at the end.
I asked the "Book of Answers".
What's the situation tonight?
It said it's not important.
I've had enough fun.
I want to take this given by Xiao Hou.
Take the small candle up.
You can light it.
Hurry up.
Still looking (for an opportunity).
I still want to talk to you.
What?
Do you have time?
You tell me.
Where should we talk?
At the boarding gate.
Let's go to the boarding gate.
Come on
You haven't sat inside today
Sit here
Stop adjusting it
Stop working
Sit down
What's wrong
Nothing
Just wanted to ask
Because I felt like I thought about it for a long time
Thought for a long time
Thought about what
Just
Just if we have
a possibility in the future
It's too far.
No.
The problem is
My impression of you is
that you are too nice.
And you are nice to everyone.
I'm already hungry.
How about I cook something for you?
I'll have some bread.
I'll take a bite of this.
No, that bread is too cold.
It smells good.
It really smells good.
So fragrant.
Prepare an egg salad sandwich.
Sandwich.
Yes, let that
WoWo and KaKa
eat it tomorrow morning.
If we go shopping,
let's bring two more friends.
Yonghao, are you going?
Sure, let's go for a walk.
I'm a bit confused.
For example,
do they really want to get close to you or what?
They don't really want to get close to me.
You subconsciously interact with them.
Whether it's friends
or during conversations.
You habitually know what to talk about
and then what to say
those words
which part comes from habit
and which part comes from the heart
That day in the car
I asked you
and then you cried
I felt like I did something wrong
No, instead you made me
Am I
Have you ever had a time when you wanted to
prove yourself
Yes, to prove it to yourself
Don't cry
No, we haven't talked about this for a long time
Sorry
Actually, a long time ago
I already had this feeling
It felt like I couldn't refuse anyone
Indeed, maybe from before
From being an engineer to opening my own shop
I couldn't offend anyone
I had to lower my stance
So I got used to hiding my emotions
Deep inside
Instead, for me, it represents that I
Really
Truly want to connect with you from the bottom of my heart
So I'm willing to let down my guard
Because for a very long time
I haven't cried for many years
So I feel that I really care about you
The reason I enjoy going on dates with you is
I can truly talk to you from the heart
And I can really
Let down my guard
But no matter what
I think as long as you are happy
I will also feel good
Really
It's just
I think
sometimes people may experience love at first sight
sometimes people develop feelings over time
this matter
they are not contradictory
right
right, so why did you agree to meet him at that moment?
yesterday I just wanted to meet Xiao Hu
so what are your thoughts afterward?
Future thoughts
At this stage
Maybe my inner balance will
lean towards Yunting
It seems that being with Yunting
feels less stressful
Are you watching the movie alone here?
What else would I be doing?
Do you think this room is colder than the others?
Really?
Because you're an ice beauty?
Bro, that joke
I like that joke
That joke is my style
I can say one sentence in German
Thank you
Do you know the most classic one?
Which classic one?
I love you
It's "I love you"
He likes
Wan Xiao originally wanted to ask Kaka out
but couldn't make it
so he's creating opportunities for himself
Tian, are you okay?
I made you some brown sugar water
Thank you, I'm really not feeling well today
Then you need to rest well
I brought you this liquid sanitary pad
and also these cooling sleep pants
They're all very useful
I have to tell you, I really love using this myself
When I'm working
I usually have to stand for several hours
I feel at ease with it
And these cooling sleep pants
A friend recommended them to me
They're very comfortable and not stuffy
Wearing them at night helps me sleep until I wake up naturally
Good things should be shared with everyone
You can buy them anytime on WeChat
through the Watsons mini program
They can be delivered in 30 minutes
Members can get them cheaper
That's really nice
Thank you, Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
You're welcome
What
This is so sudden
Is it true
Xishuangbanna
Is this real
We're going out to play
It seems like we're really going out to play
I didn't think about traveling
Yes, just go traveling
I've been to this place
It's really fun
Where is Xishuangbanna?
Yunnan
It's the place where I stayed for eight months before
Xia Xia's home ground
Let's go to the rainforest festival together
Prepare for camping and hiking
I didn't even notice
There's also camping and hiking
That's awesome
We are going to the rainforest
That hike might
be a bit tough for the girls
Here comes the problem
Look forward to it
Quickly go outside and practice
That's great
The new scene might evoke new emotions
Yes
Xia Xia is going to show her charm
Right
I really want to watch it.
In the recent conversations,
in the conversation between Xiao Hu and Liang Tian,
did everyone notice
that they all talked about
their parents' romantic relationships
and how it affects their current
views on relationships.
This kind of influence
So, what do you think
about the influence of their original families
or the fact that two people with very different backgrounds
when they interact in the future,
will they have significant disagreements
and conflicts because of this relationship?
I think there definitely will be.
Of course, this influence is not absolute.
There are also many other factors
that influence it later on.
So, I think Xiao Hu's
uncertainty and hesitation in his romantic life
are definitely
greatly influenced
by this.
I think it's really good
that he can say it like this
I think it's a kind of
very responsible behavior
and Tian Tian also understood
I think it's great, yes
Tian Tian immediately had a
gesture to ease his concerns, saying
my parents' view on my marriage
is very open-minded
yes
I don't have to get married
I think this sentence is very important
for Xiao Hu
Tian Tian's statement is
I don't have to get married at all
I think it's great
they are simply very compatible
there's no pressure on this point
at least at this moment in their conversation
yes
it seems like some things are being resolved
yes, resolved
Because at the beginning of my career
I had five years of experience with marriage and relationship programs
Children from divorced families
lack emotional support
This is not inevitable
Over the years, I think
there might be three factors that determine
whether a person will eventually love
The first one
is the relationship between the parents
The second one I think is very important
is the relationship between parents and children
It's about what kind of emotional relationship parents convey to their children
what kind of emotional relationship
The third one I think is
one's own choices
choices made later in life
These are the three factors I think
are very important in influencing a person’s final
marriage and relationship behavior
Some people
because their family is divorced
they actually desire a complete family even more
and for their own children
they hope they won't have such a lack
Yes, they actually learn to love more
First of all, if you are
a mentally healthy person,
even if you are affected
by some influences from your original family,
in the future, you may still
meet a very good person.
You cannot choose your original family,
but you can choose your future second family.
You have the choice.
So I think
it doesn't really affect
whether I meet a good person.
And actually, many times,
many people use their original family
I think people of my generation
as an excuse.
Yes, as an excuse.
It happens.
Of course, the original family definitely has an impact,
but the final choice
is in your own hands.
Yes.
That's right.
It is indeed like that.
The original family
is already a given.
Finding a loved one
is the only chance in your life
to choose a family member.
So if you say
the original family has an impact,
whether you use it as an excuse,
or as an example,
or as a negative lesson,
it is entirely up to you to decide.
A scene between the two of them
still has a lot of information to be interpreted
First, about the original family
and our personal growth
this relationship definitely exists
Yes, it does
But we don't necessarily
have harmonious couples
whose children have the ability to love
nor do children from divorced families
lack the ability to love
So why does this problem occur
It's actually what we learn in the family
from our parents
Right
It's not about learning their affection
I think affection doesn't need to be learned
Yes
It's about building intimate relationships
What we need to learn is problem-solving
the ability to resolve conflicts and disputes
You will see where Yunting's problem lies
Maybe his parents didn't give him
this kind of example
So this is his knowledge blind spot
which leads to
his avoidant personality
So you will find that he says
he can't maintain a relationship with others for more than three months
when a problem arises, he runs away
Yes, he doesn't know how to solve it
But our parents didn't teach us
We can learn by ourselves
We can completely self-study
Learn to solve problems through self-help
But I think this place, Yunting
is quite concerning
he has found his problem
but I really hope to hear
that he has a second level of realization
I need to learn about this issue
and how to solve it
He said he wants to change
Then we can have an
optimistic attitude
Liang Tian is eight years older than him
Actually, they make a pretty good team
If Liang Tian has the ability to guide him
he can help him learn to solve problems
Next,
our guests from the Half-Mature Cottage
will head to Xishuangbanna.
They will be divided into different groups.
Each group may have their own tasks
or challenges.
Let's see
what new stories will unfold
in the new environment.
Alright,
welcome to
Xishuangbanna.
Today is a tough battle.
Fight for love.
All competitions
will determine the date arrangements based on points.
Why am I getting goosebumps?
No matter what the competition is, we must win.
Everyone is really giving their all.
No one wants
to lose face in front of the girl they like.
lose face.
Brother Luo can do it.
Yunting keeps saying
we must win today.
We must win.
I really want to win.
Her eyes are full of determination.
Tian is fighting hard
I'm exhausted
Hold on
Hurry up
I'm exhausted
Alright, they already won
The last person who lost
Say to the person opposite
Hello, I love you
Your line is just two words
Okay
Hou Chengjie, you're so good
We are just a part of your game
This should be in the romance variety show
It's considered top-tier
This sense of proportion is amazing
Open the jacket
Then wrap it from the back like this
I'm in the front, I'm the one being wrapped
Destroy it
I'm so embarrassed
So scary
It won't cause any trouble, right?
Let me go
We used to interact and date frequently
Then it suddenly stopped
This is a pretty good opportunity
To talk to her about some things
Let's clarify things together
Very confused
Don't know what is
The best way to handle this
The relationships are complicated
Morning
Good morning
Your medicine
Thank you
What to do
The bacon is ready.
Time to eat.
Luckily, you are the last one.
Luckily, my plating skills are not good.
That's great.
No, wait a minute.
You brought me here today.
And let me make a pizza for you.
To make up for your mistake yesterday.
But I shipped a lot of partners.
Did you ship other people's partners in the show?
I shipped yours.
I
It's Xiao Hou.
Everyone is shipping Xiao Hou.
Especially sweet, yes.
Yes, because it was a bit too blatant.
I was completely immersed in my own world.
Okay.
This is an adult's game.
Waiting there, it's not a chance encounter with love.
It was premeditated.
Yes.
It's okay.
Being in love is the best cosmetic treatment for men.
You are so good at this.
And you said there were no little tricks.
Clearly, you are the best at it.